mac360.com 2009-06-18

# Mac360 - Privacy Policy

**Mac360’s Privacy Policy**  
Mac360 is a site developed and maintained by Ron McElfresh. We are committed to protect your privacy. The information we collect while you are visiting Mac360 is used to provide you with a more personalized and richer experience. Please read further for details.

How do we collect information?

**Your IP Address**  
Your IP address is a unique identifier Mac360 uses to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site tracking. We also use your IP address to help identify you and to gather broad and general demographic information.

**Cookies**  
We may use a feature on your Internet Web browser called a “cookie.” A cookie is a small piece of information stored on your hard drive. It assigns a unique identification number to your computer and helps us maintain your preferences between visits to provide a personalized experience for you.

We use cookies to tell us whether or not you have visited our Web site before and to track click-throughs to any of our advertisements. We also collect non-personally identifiable information, such as anonymous session numbers, with cookies.

Mac360 allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on Mac360’s pages to set and access cookies on your computer. We do not control cookies from third-party advertisers. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the privacy policy of this site. Advertisers or other companies do not have to access to cookies or cookie information from Mac360.

The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry.

**What About Personal Information? Do You Collect That?**  
We do not house or collect any personal information about you unless you knowingly and willingly provide it.

**Membership Registration**  
Mac360 may provide a registration process through which you voluntarily sign up to access the members-only features of our a site on our network. During the registration process, we may ask for your name, e-mail address, how you got to know us, your age range and your ZIP code.

Also, to make sure that nobody else can access our members-only features using your name or identity, we may ask that you create a unique user name with a password.

**Newsletter Subscription**  
Mac360 may provide newsletters for visitors to our sites. When you subscribe to our FREE newsletters, we may ask for an e-mail address to send them to. You may opt out of receiving future mailings or cancel your subscription(s) at any time.

**Contests and Promotions**  
When you enter a contest or take part in a promotion, we may ask for your name, mailing address and e-mail address. Should a third party sponsor the contest or promotion, that party will have access to this information. We need this information in order to notify our winners and, when applicable, ship the winners’ prizes.

**Does Mac360 Ever Share Information with Others?**

**Disclosure of Information to Outside Parties**  
Mac360 does not and will not share your personal information with any outside parties unless you have knowingly and willingly consented to do so (e.g., by entering a contest, promotion or sweepstakes for which we would publish a list of winners). We do collect demographic and profile data, which is aggregated and shared with advertisers. Here’s an example of what our advertisers would receive. “Of the 25,371 clicks your banner received, 38% of the those were by users between the ages of 25-34.”

**Links to Outside Third Parties**  
Mac360 may establish relationships with reputable business partners by creating a link between our sites. Mac360 chooses its business partners carefully. We are not, however, responsible for the content, maintenance or privacy policies of those sites. Once you click over to a third-party site, we encourage you to check their privacy policy.

Mac360 may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than the information practices of PanGeo Media . Users who click over to a third-party site from a link on Mac360 must be aware that Mac360 makes no warranties with regard to that site’s policies or business practices. Mac360 is not responsible for any transactions that occur between the user and the third-party site.

Please consult the other sites’ privacy policies as PanGeo Media has no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. Should a user purchase any products or services from that third-party site, the user must contact the third-party site directly regarding any disputes that might occur, including, but not limited to: delayed shipping, missing products, damaged goods, or pricing or billing discrepancies.

Mac360 is not responsible for the actions of any third-party site.

**Children’s Guidelines**  
Mac360 does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 15. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet use. Also, we strongly encourage parents to help us enforce our privacy policy by instructing their children to never provide personal information on our web sites without permission.

**Security**  
PanGeo Media has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We are able to keep your personal information safe and secure by utilizing Secure Socket Layers (SSL) encryption technology. For maximum security, we may use a secure server that encrypts all your ordering information, including your name, address, and credit-card number when applicable.

**Contacting the Web site**  
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, our Conditions of Use Agreement, our Copyright Notice, the practices of this this web site or any site within our network of sites, or your dealings with this web site or any within our network of sites, you may contact the staff of Mac360, by clicking on the Feedback link on this or any page on the site. 

By the way, Mac360 gives daily Mac updates on [Twitter](http://www.twitter.com/mac360 "Alexis and Mac360 on Twitter"). If you Twitter, give Mac360 a tweet. One more thing. Only the best Mac software gets reviewed on [Ron's NoodleMac](http://noodlemac.com/ "NoodleMac Software Updates & Reviews") site. Check it out.

_Off Topic Note_ : New Mac software updates and a special RSS feed are available on the [NoodleMac](http://noodlemac.com/ "NoodleMac") site ( _certified Mac software reviews_ ). Are you ready for a new web site that’s all about Apple but mostly for professionals? [AppleHits](http://applehits.com/ "AppleHits") covers the Mac, iPhone, iPod, and everything else that’s a hit at Apple. Guess what? [Kate Mac](http://pixobebo.com/ "Kate MacKenzie") is back after dumping Windows. One more thing: Whenever you buy from Amazon through the [Mac360 Store](http://mac360.com/index.php/mac360/store/ "Shop Amazon on Mac360") you help support Mac360.
